Guide to University of Arkansas at Fayetteville Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00086
Cubberley Education Library
University of Arkansas at Fayetteville (formerly Arkansas Industrial University, Fayetteville)
1881-1977
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00086
147 item(s)
Located in Fayetteville, Arkansas. Founded in 1871 as Arkansas Industrial University. Name changed to University of Arkansas at Fayetteville in 1899.
Land-grant colleges; Arkansas
- Arkansas Industrial University, Fayetteville, 1881-1898; 12 item(s) In bound volume: 1881/82, 1884/85, 1887/88-1888/89, 1891-1894 In bound volume with U. of Arkansas: 1895/96-1897/98 Catalog for 1885/86
- University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, 1898-1977; 134 item(s) In bound volume: Catalogs for 1898/99, 1899/1900 Separately: 1900/01-1901/02, 1903/04, 1912/13-1929/30, 1931/32-1933/34, 1935/36-1943/44, 1948/49, 1951/52
  - University of Arkansas Law Department (Little Rock), 1909-1910; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1909/10
  - University of Arkansas School of Law, 1924-1967; 13 item(s) Announcements for 1924 & 1931 Catalogs for 1945/46, 1947/48, 1949/50-1951/52, 1955/56, 1957/58-1958/59, 1961/62, 1964/65, 1966/67
  - University of Arkansas College of Agriculture (and Home Economics), 1949-1972; 15 item(s) Catalogs for 1949/50, 1954/55-1957/58, 1959/60-1964/65, 1966/67-1967/68, 1969/70, 1971/72
  - University of Arkansas College of Arts and Sciences, 1949-1977; 13 item(s) Catalogs for 1949/50, 1954/55-1957/58, 1959/60-1961/62, 1963/64-1964/65, 1966/67, 1969/70, 1971/72, 1976/77
  - University of Arkansas College of Education, 1949-1972; 11 item(s) Catalogs for 1949/50, 1953/54, 1956/57, 1959/60, 1961/62, 1963/64-1964/65, 1966/67-1967/68, 1969/70, 1971/72
  - University of Arkansas College of Engineering, 1949-1972; 10 item(s) Catalogs for 1949/50, 1954/55-1955/56, 1957/58, 1959/60, 1961/62, 1963/64-1964/65, 1966/67, 1971/72
  - Annual Report of the President..., 1949-1952; 2 item(s) Reports for 1949/50, 1951/52
  - University of Arkansas Graduate School, 1950-1970; 15 item(s) Catalogs for 1950/51, 1952/53, 1954/55-1957/58, 1959/60, 1961/62-1964/65, 1966/67-1969/70
  - University of Arkansas Register, 1953-1959; 3 item(s) Registers for 1953/54, 1954/55, 1958/59
  - University of Arkansas College of Business Administration, 1954-1972; 11 item(s) Catalogs for 1954/55-1955/56, 1957/58, 1959/60-1961/62, 1963/64-1964/65, 1966/67, 1969/70, 1971/72
  - University of Arkansas School of Architecture, 1976-77; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1976/77